<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Development on Poco A Poco | Digital Design and Video Production in Denver, Colorado</title>
    <link>http://pocoapocostudio.com/tags/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Development on Poco A Poco | Digital Design and Video Production in Denver, Colorado</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 14:02:18 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://pocoapocostudio.com/tags/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Poco a Poco Studio</title>
      <link>http://pocoapocostudio.com/blog/poco-a-poco/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2017 14:02:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pocoapocostudio.com/blog/poco-a-poco/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re reading this, you&amp;rsquo;ve caught me at a weird time. I&amp;rsquo;m transforming my freelance business, previously named Brian Liston Video Production &amp;amp; Digital Design, into Poco a Poco Studio, a small design shop focused on web development.
There are a couple reasons for this change. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to pursue what I enjoy doing most, web development, and I&amp;rsquo;m aiming to bring other designers and developers on to some of my web projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A little about the VVS portfolio theme I created for my new website</title>
      <link>http://pocoapocostudio.com/blog/vvs-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017 14:02:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pocoapocostudio.com/blog/vvs-theme/</guid>
      <description>The evolution of this site&#39;s home page, December &#39;16 to March &#39;17
 I&amp;rsquo;ve named the theme I designed for my site VVS, or &amp;ldquo;Very Very Slight&amp;rdquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s a simple theme meant for portfolio sites. What sets it apart from most portfolio themes is that it&amp;rsquo;s designed to be accessible for disabled users. I paid special attention to W3C&amp;rsquo;s Web Content Accessibility Guidelines while developing the theme, and while I haven&amp;rsquo;t yet had the chance to test it with disabled users, the theme does meet every Level A standard and many level AA standards.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>